Muhammad Fariz Fahrezi

I was a graduate of SMK country 2 cilegon with an industrial chemistry major, I had expertise in lab equipment and an understanding of chemical processes. I have experience in doing data analysis and testing the quality of chemical products. I have also been able to adapt quickly to changes in the environment and demands of the industry



Serang, Banten, Indonesia



Work Experience

September 2022 -Oktober 2022

Quality Control - PT. INDONESIA POWER SURALAYA PGU

Sampling, preparation and analysis of coal quality using TGA, CHN Analyzer, Automatic Calorimeter, and Sulfur determinator. As well as testing the analysis of water used in production

Organizational Experience

2022 - 2023

Organisasi Siswa Intra Sekolah

- · Working together on a single year program of student labor
- · Discussions during meetings for a work program
- Are responsible for running a work program
- · Organize and carry out activities to promote student creativity at school

Education

2020 - 2023

SMK Negeri 2 Cilegon Indutrial Chemistry

Hard Skills

- Laboratory Skills
- P&ID
- Ms. Excel
- Ms. Word
- Ms. Powerpoint
- Figma

Soft Skills

- Time Management
- Communication
- Public speaking
- Leadership

Language

- Indonesian Professional
- English Intermediate

Powered by **CakeResume**